# **Chokri Ben Mahjoub**

# Full Stack Developer

https://www.linkedin.com/in/chokri-ben-mahjoub/ 🔗 https://chokriben.github.io

#### **PROFILE**

Versatile and autonomous, Full Stack Developer with a passion for programming, development, analysis, and data visualization. Motivated to drive projects forward and seek innovative solutions. Consistently rewarded for success in planning and operational improvements. Experienced in policy development and staff management procedures, positively impacting overall morale and productivity.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**Full Stack Developer** Jan 2024 – present sfax, Tunisie

APBS Groupe - Intégrateur de Solutions de Gestion Sage

- Participate in all stages of design and development of software products: functional design, architecture, organic analysis and programming.
- Produce, document and correct programs in accordance with functional analysis specifications.
- Design and implement interactive and user-friendly user interfaces using Vue.js.
- Quickly identify and resolve problems encountered during development or in production.

Technical environment: Javascript, Vue is, Dot.Net, SQL server, Devexpress, PrimeVue, Docker, Crystal Report, Git,

**Full Stack Developer** 

Infotech Consulting Services ICS

Dec 2022 - Dec 2023 Sfax, Tunisia

- Participate in the creation of new APIs, including testing using of postman to check their operation (backend side)
- Develop new services on the backend side to support load the necessary
- Create new interfaces and pages on the frontend side to provide improved user experience

Technical environment: Laravel, API Postman, Nuxt.js, Vue.js 3, Docker, JIRA, MySQL

Developer Nov 2021 - Sep 2022 Logicom

- Follow-up and processing of customer complaints Development in the various ERP modules (management commercial, stock management site management, production, checkout, etc.)

- Testing and verification of the developed modules
- Deployment of states (Crystal Report) Technical environment: C#, Visual Basic, Crystal Report et SQL, Php

sfax, Tunisie

## Intern (end-of-study internship)

Leader tec Engineering

- Development of a stock management application that allows:

- Manage suppliers, customer orders,
- products.. Management of invoices, quotes...
- Technical environment: Php, java, javascript, bootstrap, html5, android studio

### **EDUCATION**

Master in development of computer systems and networks specializing in software engineering and new technology at Iset Sfax

Higher Institute of Technological Studies of Sfax - ISET

Nov 2022 – Dec 2024 sfax, Tunisia

Feb 2020 - Jul 2020

sfax, Tunisie

Fundamental degree in computer science

Higher Institute of Computer Science and Multimedia Sfax-ISIMS

Sep 2017 – Jun 2020 sfax, Tunisie

**BACCALAUREATE IN MATHEMATICS** 

Majida Boulila High School

Sep 2012 – Jul 2017 sfax, Tunisie

**SKILLS** 

Web development — JavaScript , Php , Laravel ,

symfony, React Js, Vue Js, Dot.Net, Blazor,

**PROGRAMMING** — C , C# ,Java,j2EE, Python,

Operating system — Linux (Ubuntu), Windows,

Database mastery — MySQL, SQLServer, Mongodb,

**Other** — ILLUSTRATOR, Adobe PhotoShop | Big

data, Hadoop, Odoo, Docker

**PROJECTS** 

car rental website Apr 2019 – Apr 2019

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Technologies used: css,Html5, Javascript, Php

**INTERESTS** 

sport | Extracurricular Activities

**LANGUAGES** 

Anglais 

● ● ● ●